javascripting.com 2004-06-08

# FreeScripts.com: Privacy Statement

#### Privacy Statement

This web site is maintained by Command-O Software, Inc. 

Our postal address is:  
Command-O Software, Inc.  
PO Box 12200  
Jackson Hole, WY, 83002  
USA 

This site collects no personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. A user's personally identifying information will not be transferred to any third party unless otherwise stated at the time of collection. 

The information we collect is used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. Individuals have the ability to stop their information from being used for marketing and promotional purposes by removing their e-mail address from our mailing using the form on our home page. Any personally identifying information collected by this site from children is used for editorial participation and feedback purposes, together with any other purposes that will be described where the information is collected, and will not be transferred to any third party.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive information for which you provided us your address. You may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

This web site, as well as some others maintained by Command-O Software may place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. These cookies help our web site better serve the user, and are recorded specifically for that purpose. 

**KIDS:** Be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself to anyone over the Internet. 

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **Solution Center** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
